https://stoneslinger.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We, at W.K. Dahms Mfg. Ltd. (referred to hereinafter as W. K. Dahms), approach our communications on the Internet with respect for, and commitment to protecting, your privacy rights. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you on the W. K. Dahms Website. We hope that this disclosure below in the form of questions and answers will help increase your confidence in our site and enhance your experience on the Internet.
Personal information is any information about an identifiable person other than the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization.
How does the W.K. Dahms Site collect personal information from you?
We collect personal information from you only for the purposes we identify to you at or prior to the time we collect such personal information. We do not require this information in order for you to obtain access, to surf or to view the content on the W. K. Dahms Site.
For those few activities on our Site where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary (for example, when you contact us with a question), you will know because the purposes for which your personal information is to be used will be identified to you. For those activities, we may collect, for example, your name, street address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address and postal code. We will not collect more information than is necessary.
Does W. K. Dahms collect or use information collected from you with technology?
The W. K. Dahms Site collects some information about you using technology, so it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our Site, your IP address is collected so that we know how many visits we have had by separate individuals. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the Internet like your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or your firm or company. This information is not necessarily personally identifiable.
How does W.K. Dahms use the personal information it has collected from you?
Providing personal information is up to you, our visitor. We collect personally identifiable information to respond to your questions or comments and/or to send out brochures and other information on our products or our company. We may ask visitors providing e-mail addresses to let us know if they would like further information or updates from us or our site and only those who request it will receive follow-up e-mail or other communications from us.  In that case, we may also offer visitors an “opt-out” option at any time they wish to cease receiving e-mails or other information from us.
We will only use such information for the purposes of (1) administering certain programs as identified to you at the time of collection; and (2) for statistical and marketing analysis, in a form where the information is no longer identifiable with you.
To whom will W.K. Dahms provide your personal information?
Personal information is used solely by us. We will not disclose such information, other than as follows:
(a)  to third party service providers with whom W. K. Dahms has a contractual agreement, which includes appropriate privacy standards, for the purpose of (i) performing functions such as data processing, database services or information technology support; and (ii) providing insurance for product liability claims on behalf of W. K. Dahms; and
(b)  to comply with any legal actions like a court order or to protect the safety and security of guests and the W. K. Dahms Site.
We will let you know at the time the information is collected if such third-party sharing is anticipated, will identify the types of businesses at the area of collection, will describe the information we will share (like your mail or e-mail address) and will only share data if you agree.  We will share personal data only with those who have agreed to follow policies that share our high standards of privacy.
Links and Disclaimer of Linked Sites
Please note that once you have clicked on a link on the W. K. Dahms Site, you may leave the W. K. Dahms Site to a site which is no longer under the control of W. K. Dahms, and to which our Privacy Policy no longer applies. You must read the Privacy Policy, if any, of each linked site to see how your personal information will be handled on their site.
What type of security does W.K. Dahms provide?
The importance of security for all personal information collected through the W. K. Dahms Site is of utmost concern to us. We have taken technical, contractual, administrative and physical security steps to protect the personal information collected from you on the W. K. Dahms Site with a level of security appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information collected. Our security measures are periodically reviewed.
Who to contact with questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy?
If you need further assistance, please contact the W. K. Dahms Privacy Officer either by writing to us at:
W. K. Dahms Mfg. Ltd. P.O. Box 520 3074 Sawmill Road St. Jacobs, OntarioCanada N0B 2N0 Phone: 519-664-3414 Fax: 519-664-2082 Attention: Privacy Officer
or by visiting the W. K. Dahms website and submitting your inquiry via email.
Please note that this Privacy Policy is with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information through the W. K. Dahms Site only.
© Copyright 2019 W.K. Dahms Mfg. Ltd.
Privacy Policy
Site Map
